Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Records SC0656
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2000-079
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory: Adults scoring key & answer sheets (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory: Adults special research ed. NFER (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory: Adults Arabic translation (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Bell, The School Inventory (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Chan, Shau Wing, Chinese Writing Stroke Chart 1944 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Cole, Stewart, Charting Intercultural Education 1946 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Anderson, H. Dewey, Our California State Taxes 1937 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Bennett, M. K., Price Relatives for Individual Commodities 1949 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Buell, Robert K., California Stepping Stones 1950 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Bernreuter, Robert G., The Personality Inventory: translations in Dutch, French, Spanish, Japanese, etc. (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory Specimen Set (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory test booklets (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory permissions (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory answer sheets (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory scoring keys (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory manuals, norm sheets, report sheets, Spanish translation (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory IBM scoring keys (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory Klein Institute test booklets (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory Klein Institute personal data sheets (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory Associated Personnel Technicians, Inc. (APT) imprint test booklets (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Bernreuter, The Personality Inventory MTS Co. (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Richards, L.W. and G. L Richards, Geologic History at a Glance- various printings (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Sands, Lester B. and Richard E. Gross, History of Education Chart (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory Slovak/Czech translation (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory APT (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory French translation (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory French & Polish translations (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory Italian translation (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory Hindi translation (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory Spanish & Bengali translations (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory Spanish translations (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory NFER 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Bell, The Adjustment Inventory school inventory (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Borow, Henry, College Inventory of Academic Adjustment (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Burch, Mary C., Stanford Tests of Comprehension of Literature 1928 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Byrd, Oliver E., Health Attitude Scale (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Byrd, Oliver E., Personal Health Inventory (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Byrd, Oliver E., Patient’s Self-History Form (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Dearborn, Terry H., A Checklist for the Survey of Health and Physical Education Programs in Secondary Schools (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Dearborn, Terry H., College Health Knowledge Test (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Eells, Walter C. and David Segel, Stanford Tests for Junior Colleges Test in English (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Espinosa, Aurelio, The Stanford Spanish Tests (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - McReynolds, Paul and James T. Ferguson, Hospital Adjustment Scale (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Fitzwater, James P., Fitzwater Educational Film Appraisal Scale (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Hinkle, George and Francis R. Johnson, The Form for the Term or Research Paper (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Jensen, Milton B., Stanford Educational Aptitudes Test (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Johns, Edward B., Health Practice Inventory (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Bernreuter/Bell correspondence (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - SVIB-SCII MinComp Corp 1973- (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - SVIB-SCII Mincomp Manual (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - SVIB-SCII MinComp Forms thru 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - SVIB-SCII Mincomp Testin/Evalution/Guidance (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - SVIB-SCII IPR French-Canadian ed. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - SVIB-SCII IPR French-Canadian & English eds. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - SVIB-SCII IPR French-Canadian forms (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - SVIB-SCII Psi Can Consulting Ltd. (Canada) T325 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - SVIB-SCII Saville & Holdsworth Ltd. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - SVIB-SCII miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - SVIB-SCII Spanish ed. M, W (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - SVIB-SCII Italian ed. M, W (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - SVIB-SCII Korean ed. T399R (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - SVIB-SCII Portuguese ed. T399, M (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - SVIB-SCII Dutch ed. Meijan Reports on T399 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - SVIB-SCII Flemish-Belgium ed. M, W (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - SVIB-SCII NIER British ed. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - SVIB-SCII Dutch T399 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - SVIB-SCII Bengali ed. M adaptation (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - SVIB-SCII Danish ed. M (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - SVIB-SCII French ed. Clerebaut M, W, T399R (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - SVIB-SCII French ed. EAP forms (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - SVIB-SCII German ed. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - SVIB-SCII Hindi ed. M (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - SVIB-SCII Indian ed. Calcutta University M (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - SVIB-SCII Iranian ed. T399 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - SVIB-SCII Irish ed. (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - SVIB-SCII miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - SVIB-SCII Form T325 test (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - SVIB-SCII manuals & blanks, various editions (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Between Pacific Tides Artwork (photos, sketches) including dust jacket photo for 1968 edition (Box 19 os)
  - Bird’s eye view of S. U. Press facilities (Box 19 os)
  - One Day in the World’s Press; Fourteen Great Newspapers on a Day of Crisis [November 2, 1956] (Box 19 os)
  - Original art for Ivan Benson’s Mark Twain’s Western Years (Box 19 os)
  - Artwork for Mackey & Sooy, Early California Costumes (Box 19 os)
  - California Stepping Stones – records produced by Pax Productions [15 ¾ inch wide] of dramatizations produced by The Junior Leagues of California, with two copies of the Teachers’ Utilization Guide and one copy of the Historical Time Line (Box 20 os)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2007-327
  - Chester Kerr, “The Kerr Report Revisited,” reprint from Scholarly Publishing, October 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “The Story of Stanford University Press,” pamphlet, Feb. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fruge, August, “A Report on University Publishing in Latin-American Countries,” 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A Report on the University of California Printing Department, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Richards and Richards, “Geologic History at a Glance,” 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” proofs 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” letter and outline 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” project ideas 1951-52 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” letter and typescript 1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” typescript and letter by Elizabeth (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” typescript (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bartky and Doyle, “Your Democracy,” typescript of selected parts (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – newspaper installments, typescripts (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – installments, printed sheets (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – installments for Junior Scholastic, typescripts (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – Junior Scholastic, #1-12 (incomplete) 1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – Junior Scholastic, #13-29 (incomplete) 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – photos and binding example (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – illustrations (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Your Rugged Constitution – illustrations (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Horse Power Days – negatives of images of carriages (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos for part I (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos for part II (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos for part III (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - McClure, California Landmarks – photos pages 110-131 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Adams, Yosemite – maps (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Collins, Horse Power Days – printing negatives (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pickwell, Amphibians and reptiles of the Pacific states – illustrations and photos (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Records, 1951-2013; Accession ARCH-2014-036
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2013 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2013 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2012 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2012 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2011 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2011 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2010 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2010 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2009 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2009 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2008 (Box 2, Item 11)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2008 (different cover) (Box 2, Item 12)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2007 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2007 (Box 2, Item 14)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2006 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2006 (Box 2, Item 16)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2005 (Box 2, Item 17)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2005 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2004 (Box 2, Item 19)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2004 (Box 2, Item 20)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2003 (Box 2, Item 21)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2003 (Box 2, Item 22)
  - SUP Board of Overseers, 1998 Sep 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SUP Board of Overseers, 1999 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Press Board of Overseers (SUP History) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SUP - Correspondences (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Publisher Briefs & Author, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SUP Report to Faulty & Staff, 1962 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - SUP - Press Fiances and Budgets - Part 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SUP - Press Fiances and Budgets - Part 2, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SUP - Press Fiances and Budgets - Part 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SUP - Press Fiances and Budgets - Part 4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letters of Appraisal, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Warren Christopher - Foreign Policy for a New Era, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - LES Material (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - SUP Fiances Reports, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - SUP/ CUP, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - SUP Proposal For the 1990s and Beyond, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Electrongic Imprint Proposal, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Re: Wayne State Press, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2002 (Box 1, Item 19)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2002 (Box 1, Item 20)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2001 (Box 1, Item 21)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2001 (Box 1, Item 22)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 2000 (Box 1, Item 23)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 2000 (Box 1, Item 24)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1999 (Box 1, Item 25)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1999 (Box 1, Item 26)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1998 (Box 1, Item 27)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1998 (Box 1, Item 28)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1997 (Box 1, Item 29)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1997 (Box 1, Item 29)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1996 (Box 1, Item 30)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1995 (Box 1, Item 32)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1995 (Box 1, Item 33)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1994 (Box 1, Item 34)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1994 (Box 1, Item 35)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1993-94, 1993 -1994 (Box 1, Item 36)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1993 (Box 1, Item 37)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Item 38)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1992 (Box 1, Item 39)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1991-92, 1991- 1992 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1991 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1990-91, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Item 42)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1990 (Box 1, Item 43)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1989 (Box 1, Item 45)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1988 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1986-87, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1986 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1985-1986, 1985-86 (Box 1, Item 51)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1985 (Box 1, Item 52)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Item 53)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1984 (Box 1, Item 54)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall/Winter 1983-84, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Item 55)
  - Stanford University Press - Spring 1983 (Box 1, Item 56)
  - Stanford University Press - Fall 1982 (Box 1, Item 57)
  - Stanford University Press Books - Spring 1982 (Box 1, Item 58)
  - Stanford University Press Books - Fall 1981 (Box 1, Item 59)
  - Stanford University Press Books - Spring 1981 (Box 1, Item 60)
  - Stanford University Press Books - Fall 1980 (Box 1, Item 61)
  - Stanford University Press Books - Spring 1980 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - About Stanford University Press Pamphlet, 1980 (Box 1, Item 63)